A Guide to the Additional Papers of the Randolph Family of Edgehill (1830)1840-1947
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Randolph Dickins to his mother Margaret Harvie Dickins 1880 January-May (Box-folder 1:21)
- Randolph Dickins to his mother Margaret Harvie Dickins 1880 June-September; 1884 (Box-folder 1:22)
- Randolph Dickins to his niece Theodora Wight Keim 1885; 1893 (Box-folder 1:23)
- E.J. Harvie to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1862 February 17 (Box-folder 1:24)
- Sally Heath to Harriot Dickins Wight n.d. (Box-folder 1:25)
- Herbert [] to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1863 (Box-folder 1:26)
- John O. Keim to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1892 November 15 (Box-folder 2:1)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her mother Harriot Dickins Wight n.d. (Box-folder 2:2)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her mother Harriot Dickins Wight 1888-1889 (Box-folder 2:3)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her mother Harriot Dickins Wight 1889 (Box-folder 2:4)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her mother Harriot Dickins Wight 1890; n.d. (Box-folder 2:5)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her mother Harriot Dickins Wight 1914 June-July (Box-folder 2:6)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her mother Harriot Dickins Wight 1914 August (Box-folder 2:7)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her mother Harriot Dickins Wight 1914 September-October (Box-folder 2:8)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her husband John May Keim 1905; 1909 (Box-folder 2:9)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her husband John May Keim n.d. (Box-folder 2:10)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her husband John May Keim n.d. (Box-folder 2:11)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her husband John May Keim n.d. (Box-folder 2:12)
- Theodora Wight Keim to her husband John May Keim n.d. (Box-folder 2:13)
- Colonel J. B. Kershaw to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1861-1890 (Box-folder 2:14)
- Letter to the Army from Ladies of Fighting Creek 1864 April 9 (Box-folder 2:15)
- Letters to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1859-1863 (Box-folder 3:1)
- Letters to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1864-1866 (Box-folder 3:2)
- Letters to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1868-1890 (Box-folder 3:3)
- Letters to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1892-1895 (Box-folder 3:4)
- Letters to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins n.d. (Box-folder 3:5)
- Letters to Francis Asbury Dickins 1858-1880 (Box-folder 3:6)
- Letters to Margaret Harvie Dickins 1855; 1861; n.d. (Box-folder 3:7)
- Letters to Margaret Harvie Dickins 1879 (Box-folder 3:8)
- Letters to Theodora Wight Keim 1892-1947 (Box-folder 3:9)
- Letters to Harriot Dickins Wight 1862-1868 (Box-folder 3:10)
- Letters to Harriot Dickins Wight 1869-1879 (Box-folder 3:11)
- Letters to Harriot Dickins Wight 1880, 1887 (Box-folder 3:12)
- Letters to Harriot Dickins Wight 1888-1914 (Box-folder 3:13)
- Letters to Harriot Dickins Wight n.d. (Box-folder 3:14)
- Maria Randolph Mason to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1892 October 20 (Box-folder 4:1)
- Alice Meikleham to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1892 November (Box-folder 4:2)
- Miscellaneous items 1879; 1887 (Box-folder 4:3)
- Miscellaneous letters 1830; 1909; n.d. (Box-folder 4:4)
- Miscellaneous letters n.d. (Box-folder 4:5)
- Photographs n.d. (Box-folder 4:6)
- Poem by a Confederate Soldier n.d. (Box-folder 4:7)
- Poems n.d. (Box-folder 4:8)
- Cary Ruffin Randolph (obituary) n.d. (Box-folder 4:9)
- Jane H. Randolph to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1862 (Box-folder 4:10)
- Jane Randolph to cousin Harriot Dickins Wight n.d. (Box-folder 4:11)
- [Louisa Randolph] to Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1861-1864 (Box-folder 4:12)
- L. A. Randolph to her granddaughter Harriot Dickins Wight n.d. (Box-folder 4:13)
- Ellen Ruffin to Margaret Harvie Dickins 1861 (Box-folder 4:14)
- Alice L. Tapscote to Harriot Dickins Wight 1909 (Box-folder 4:15)
- Grace M. Wight 1867 (Box-folder 4:16)
- Grace M. Wight to daughter in-law Harriot Dickins Wight n.d. (Box-folder 4:17)
- Harriot Dickins Wight to sister Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1887 (Box-folder 4:18)
- Harriot Dickins Wight to sister Frances Margaret (Fanny) Dickins 1887 (Box-folder 4:19)
- Harriot Dickins Wight to Frank Dickins Jr. 1869 December 10 (Box-folder 5:1)
- Harriot Dickins Wight to her mother Margaret Harvie Dickins 1861-1862 (Box-folder 5:2)
- Harriot Dickins Wight to her mother Margaret Harvie Dickins 1871-1872 (Box-folder 5:3)
- Harriot Dickins Wight to her mother Margaret Harvie Dickins 1873 ;1887; n.d. (Box-folder 5:4)
- Harriot Dickins Wight to her mother Margaret Harvie Dickins 1892; n.d. (Box-folder 5:5)
- Harriot Dickins Wight to Grace M. Wight n.d. (Box-folder 5:6)
- Harriot Dickins Wight to Henry Theodore Wight n.d. (Box-folder 5:7)
- Harriot Dickins Wight from Theodora 1865 November (Box-folder 5:8)
- Harriot Dickins Wight papercuttings n.d. (Box-folder 5:9)
- William W. Wight to Harriot Dickins Wight n.d. (Box-folder 5:10)
- Receipts and Expenditures of the United States 1826 (Volume 5:11)
- Daily Dispatch Richmond Newspaper 1875 October 27
- Account book of Harriot Dickins Wight 1882-1892
- Harry gardner to Samuel Spring Gardner 1863 February 8
- Photograph of Theodora Keim, Harriot Dickins Wight and African Americans Mammy and Uncle Robert 1886
- Confederate Column 1896